<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
             xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
             xmlns:b="urn:import:com.github.gwtbootstrap.client.ui">
    
    <ui:with field='res' type='com.eprovement.poptavka.resources.StyleResource' />
    <ui:style>
        .question {
        font-weight: bold;
        size: 14px;
        }
    </ui:style>

    <g:ScrollPanel styleName='{res.initial.scrollContainer}'>
        <g:HTMLPanel styleName='{res.common.howItWorksContainer}'>
            <h1>
                Frequently Asked Questions
            </h1>
            <h3>How does Want-Something.com works?</h3>
            <g:Label addStyleNames='{style.question}'>
                1. Tell us about your project
            </g:Label>
            <g:Label>
                Select a project category that best matches your project or any other need. You will be asked few questions via online form to help us match the right professional for your job. Want-Something.com has thousands professionals specializing in over 4,600 categories and 33,000 US localities.
            </g:Label>
            <br />
            <g:Label addStyleNames='{style.question}'>
                2. Receive offers
            </g:Label>
            <g:Label>
                After your project is approved by Customer Support you'll receive offers from local professionals. You can compare offers, check reviews or negotiate the price before you select the right professional. 
            </g:Label>
            <br />
            <g:Label addStyleNames='{style.question}'>
                3. Get it done
            </g:Label>
            <g:Label>
                Selected professional starts working on the project. Once the project is finished  both parties, client and professional, post feedback to each other. 
            </g:Label>
            <g:Label>
                We are here to help local business grow across the U.S.
            </g:Label>
            <br />
            <h3>What is Want-Something.com?</h3>
            <g:Label>
                Want-Something.com is a consumer service that helps family owners, managers or companies to accomplish their projects or satisfy their demands. Whether customers need to paint their home, learn a new language, or plan their daughter's birthday party.
            </g:Label>
            <g:Label>
                Want-Something.com is the easiest and most dependable way to hire the right professional. Customers tell us what they need, and we introduce them to several qualified professionals.
                Then, customers compare and hire the pro that's right for them.
            </g:Label>
            <br />
            <g:Label>
                Want-Something.com searches for people or businesses in your area that can address your needs. Need your house painted? Need your lawn mowed?  Need your car fixed? Want-Something.com does the search for you so that you don't waste your time browsing through Internet.
            </g:Label>            
            <br />
            <br />

            <g:SimplePanel ui:field="footer"/>
        </g:HTMLPanel>
    </g:ScrollPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>
